A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1939
  - United States, 1939; 1939/200
    - United States - (Am-As), 1939 (Box 170, Folder 1238)
    - United States - (Association of Documentary Film Producers), 1939 (Box 170, Folder 1239)
    - United States - (As-Be), 1939 (Box 171, Folder 1240)
    - United States - (Bi-Bz), 1939 (Box 171, Folder 1241)
    - United States - (C-Co), 1939 (Box 171, Folder 1242)
    - United States - (Co-Dz), 1939 (Box 171, Folder 1243)
    - United States - (E-F), 1939 (Box 171, Folder 1244)
    - United States - (G-Gr), 1939 (Box 171, Folder 1245)
    - United States - (Gr-Ho), 1939 (Box 172, Folder 1246)
    - United States - (Ho-Ino), 1939 (Box 172, Folder 1247)
    - United States - (Ins-K), 1939 (Box 172, Folder 1248)
    - United States - (L), 1939 (Box 172, Folder 1249)
    - United States - (Ma), 1939 (Box 172, Folder 1250)
    - United States - (M), 1939 (Box 172, Folder 1251)
    - United States - (Na), 1939 (Box 173, Folder 1252)
    - United States - (Na-Pa), 1939 (Box 173, Folder 1253)
    - United States - (Pe-Re), 1939 (Box 173, Folder 1254)
    - United States - (Ri-Sc), 1939 (Box 173, Folder 1255)
    - United States - (Sc-So), 1939 (Box 173, Folder 1256)
    - United States - (Sp-Sz), 1939 (Box 173, Folder 1257)
    - United States - T-U.S. (Fisheries), 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1258)
    - United States - (U.S. Labor - U.S. Public Health Service), 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1259)
    - United States - (U.S. State Department), 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1260)
    - United States - (U.S. Senate - Wi), 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1261)
    - United States - (Wi-Z), 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1262)
    - United States - State Department, 1939 (Box 549, Folder 3661)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1939; 1939/200.A
      - United States, 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1263)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1939; 1939/200.D
      - United States, 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1263)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/200.E
      - United States, 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1263)
      - United States - (C-H), 1939 (Box 174, Folder 1264)
      - United States - (K-Z), 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1265)
    - United States - Malaria, 1939; 1939/200.I
      - United States, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1266)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/200.R
      - United States, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1266)
      - United States - (Baltimore Museum of Art), 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1267)
      - United States, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1268)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/200.S
      - United States - Social Science Research Council, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1269)
  - Alabama, 1939; 1939/201
    - Alabama, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
  - Arizona, 1939; 1939/203
    - Arizona, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
  - Arkansas, 1939; 1939/204
    - Arkansas, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
  - California, 1939; 1939/205
    - California, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
    - California - Medical Sciences, 1939; 1939/205.A
      - California, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
    - California - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/205.E
      - California, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
    - California - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/205.R
      - California, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1270)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1939; 1939/206
    - Canal Zone, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
  - Colorado, 1939; 1939/207
    - Colorado, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
    - Colorado - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/207.R
      - Colorado, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
    - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/207.S
      - Colorado, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
  - Connecticut, 1939; 1939/208
    - Connecticut, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
  - Florida, 1939; 1939/211
    - Florida, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
  - Georgia, 1939; 1939/212
    - Georgia, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 1271)
  - Hawaii, 1939; 1939/214
    - Hawaii, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1272)
  - Idaho, 1939; 1939/215
    - Idaho, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1272)
  - Illinois, 1939; 1939/216
    - Illinois, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1272)
  - Kansas, 1939; 1939/219
    - Kansas, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Kentucky, 1939; 1939/220
    - Kentucky, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Louisiana, 1939; 1939/221
    - Louisiana, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Maine, 1939; 1939/222
    - Maine, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Maryland, 1939; 1939/223
    - Maryland, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Massachusetts, 1939; 1939/224
    - Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Mississippi, 1939; 1939/227
    - Mississippi, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1273)
  - Montana, 1939; 1939/229
    - Montana, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - Nevada, 1939; 1939/231
    - Nevada, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - New Jersey, 1939; 1939/233
    - New Jersey, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - New Mexico, 1939; 1939/234
    - New Mexico, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - North Carolina, 1939; 1939/236
    - North Carolina, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
    - North Carolina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1939; 1939/236.D
      - North Carolina, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - North Dakota, 1939; 1939/237
    - North Dakota, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - Ohio, 1939; 1939/238
    - Ohio, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1274)
  - Oregon, 1939; 1939/240
    - Oregon, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
  - Pennsylvania, 1939; 1939/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
    - Pennsylvania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1939; 1939/241.D
      - Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
    - Pennsylvania - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/241.R
      - Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
  - Rhode Island, 1939; 1939/244
    - Rhode Island, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
  - South Carolina, 1939; 1939/246
    - South Carolina, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
    - South Carolina - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/246.R
      - South Carolina, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
  - South Dakota, 1939; 1939/247
    - South Dakota, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1275)
  - Tennessee, 1939; 1939/248
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health - Syphilis - TVA, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1276)
    - Tennessee - TVA, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1277)
  - Texas, 1939; 1939/249
    - Texas, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1277)
  - Utah, 1939; 1939/250
    - Utah, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1277)
  - Virginia, 1939; 1939/252
    - Virginia, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1277)
    - Virginia - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/252.S
      - Virginia, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1277)
  - Wisconsin, 1939; 1939/255
    - Wisconsin, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1278)
  - Wyoming, 1939; 1939/256
    - Wyoming, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1278)
  - Virgin Islands, 1939; 1939/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1939 (Box 176, Folder 1278)
  - South America, 1939; 1939/300
    - South America, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1279)
    - South America - Reports, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1280)
    - South America - Reports, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1281)
    - South America - South American Academies and Learned Societies, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1282)
    - South America - South American Academies and Learned Societies - U.S. History, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1283)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1939; 1939/300.A
      - South America, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1284)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1939; 1939/300.D
      - South America, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1284)
    - South America - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/300.R
      - South America, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 1284)
      - South America, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1285)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/300.S
      - South America, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1285)
  - Argentina, 1939; 1939/301
    - Argentina, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1286)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/301.E
      - Argentina, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1286)
  - Bolivia, 1939; 1939/303
    - Bolivia, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
  - Brazil, 1939; 1939/305
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1939; 1939/305.O
      - KUM-1 Kumm, Henry W. "Effects of certain Combinations of Temperature and Relative Humidity upon the Longevity of Adult Aedes Aegypti", 1939 (Box 560, Folder 3804)
  - Chile, 1939; 1939/309
    - Chile, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/309.E
      - Chile, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
    - Chile - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/309.R
      - Chile, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
  - Colombia, 1939; 1939/311
    - Colombia, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
  - Costa Rica, 1939; 1939/313
    - Costa Rica, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/313.E
      - Costa Rica, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1287)
  - Cuba, 1939; 1939/315
    - Cuba, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1288)
    - Cuba - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/315.E
      - Cuba, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1289)
  - Ecuador, 1939; 1939/317
    - Ecuador, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1289)
  - Guatemala, 1939; 1939/319
    - Guatemala, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1289)
  - Mexico, 1939; 1939/323
    - Mexico - (A-E), 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1289)
    - Mexico - (F-Z), 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1290)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/323.R
      - Mexico, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1290)
  - Nicaragua, 1939; 1939/325
    - Nicaragua, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1290)
    - Nicaragua - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/325.E
      - Nicaragua, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 1290)
  - Panama, 1939; 1939/327
    - Panama, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
    - Panama - Nursing, 1939; 1939/327.C
      - Panama, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/327.E
      - Panama, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
    - Panama - Hookworm, 1939; 1939/327.H
      - Panama, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
    - Panama - Malaria, 1939; 1939/327.I
      - MEA-1 Mead, Pauline M. "Statistical Analysis of Malaria in Panama", 1939 (Box 560, Folder 3805)
  - Paraguay, 1939; 1939/329
    - Paraguay, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
  - Peru, 1939; 1939/331
    - Peru, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/331.E
      - Peru, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
  - El Salvador, 1939; 1939/333
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/333.E
      - El Salvador, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
  - Dominican Republic, 1939; 1939/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
  - Uruguay, 1939; 1939/337
    - Uruguay, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1291)
  - Venezuela, 1939; 1939/339
    - Venezuela - (A-G) - Health, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1292)
    - Venezuela - Health, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1293)
    - Venezuela - Health, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1294)
    - Venezuela - (H-Z), 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1295)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1295)
  - Great Britain, 1939; 1939/400
    - Great Britain, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1296)
  - England, 1939; 1939/401
    - England - (A-C), 1939 (Box 179, Folder 1296)
    - England - (F-M), 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1297)
    - England - (N-Z), 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1298)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/401.E
      - England, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1299)
    - England - Public Health Education, 1939; 1939/401.L
      - England, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1299)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/401.R
      - England, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1299)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/401.S
      - England, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1299)
  - Ireland, 1939; 1939/403
    - Ireland, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1300)
  - Scotland, 1939; 1939/405
    - Scotland, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1300)
    - Scotland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/405.E
      - Scotland, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1300)
  - Australia, 1939; 1939/410
    - Australia, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1300)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/410.E
      - Australia, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1300)
  - New Zealand, 1939; 1939/418
    - New Zealand, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1301)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1301)
  - Fiji, 1939; 1939/419
    - Fiji - Public Health Educations, 1939; 1939/419.J
      - Fiji, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1301)
  - Caribbean Region, 1939; 1939/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1301)
  - Guyana, 1939; 1939/423
    - British Guiana, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1302)
    - Guyana - Tuberculosis, 1939; 1939/423.T
      - British Guiana, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1302)
  - Belize, 1939; 1939/425
    - British Honduras, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1302)
  - Canada, 1939; 1939/427
    - Canada - (A-L), 1939 (Box 180, Folder 1302)
    - Canada - (M-Z), 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1303)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/427.E
      - Canada, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1304)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1939; 1939/427.L
      - Canada, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1304)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/427.R
      - Canada, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1304)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/427.S
      - Canada, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1304)
  - West Indies, 1939; 1939/431
    - West Indies, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1305)
  - Barbados, 1939; 1939/435
    - Barbados, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1305)
  - Jamaica, 1939; 1939/437
    - Jamaica, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1305)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1305)
  - St. Kitts, 1939; 1939/439
    - St. Kitts, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1305)
  - India, 1939; 1939/464
    - India - Administration, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1306)
    - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1307)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1939; 1939/464.A
      - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1307)
    - India - Nursing, 1939; 1939/464.C
      - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/464.E
      - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1939; 1939/464.L
      - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1939; 1939/464.O
      - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/464.S
      - India, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
    - India - Mysore, 1939; 1939/464.1
      - Mysore, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
    - India - Travancore, 1939; 1939/464.5
      - Travancore, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1308)
  - Iraq, 1939; 1939/470
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1939; 1939/470.I
      - Iraq, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1309)
  - Straits Settlements, 1939; 1939/473
    - Straits Settlements - Declinations, 1939; 1939/473.F
      - Straits Settlements, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1309)
  - Rhodesia, 1939; 1939/483
    - Rhodesia, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1309)
  - North Africa Region, 1939; 1939/485
    - Egypt, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1309)
  - Southern Africa Region, 1939; 1939/487
    - South Africa Region, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1309)
  - France, 1939; 1939/500
    - France - (A-I), 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1309)
    - France - (F-Z) - Health, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1310)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/500.E
      - France, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1310)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/500.R
      - France, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1310)
  - Asia, 1939; 1939/600
    - Asia, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1311)
  - China, 1939; 1939/601
    - China - (General) - Administration, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1311)
    - China - (A-C), 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1312)
    - China - Health, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1313)
    - China - (H-Z), 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1314)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1939; 1939/601.A
      - China, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1314)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/601.E
      - China, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1315)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/601.R
      - China, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 1315)
  - Japan, 1939; 1939/609
    - Japan, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/609.E
      - Japan, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
  - Thailand, 1939; 1939/617
    - Thailand, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/617.E
      - Thailand, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
  - Holland, 1939; 1939/650
    - Netherlands, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
    - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
    - Holland - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1316)
  - Europe, 1939; 1939/700
    - Europe - (G-K), 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1317)
    - Europe - (K-M), 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1318)
    - Europe - (N-Z), 1939 (Box 183, Folder 1319)
  - Austria, 1939; 1939/705
    - Austria - (A), 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1320)
    - Austria - (B-Z), 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1321)
  - Belgium, 1939; 1939/707
    - Belgium, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1321)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/707.R
      - Belgium, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1321)
  - Congo (Zaire), 1939; 1939/709
    - Congo (Zaire), 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
  - Yugoslavia, 1939; 1939/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
    - Yugoslavia - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/710.R
      - Yugoslavia, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
  - Bulgaria, 1939; 1939/711
    - Bulgaria, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
    - Bulgaria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/711.E
      - Bulgaria, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1939; 1939/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
  - Denmark, 1939; 1939/713
    - Denmark, 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1323)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/713.E
      - Denmark, 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1323)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/713.R
      - Denmark, 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1323)
  - Scandinavia, 1939; 1939/716
    - Scandinavia, 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1323)
  - Germany, 1939; 1939/717
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1324)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Murrow Committee), 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1325)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Murrow Committee), 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1326)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Murrow Committee), 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1327)
    - Germany - (A-K), 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1328)
    - Germany - (L-S), 1939 (Box 185, Folder 1329)
    - Germany - (S-Z), 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1330)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/717.E
      - Germany, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1330)
    - Germany - Declinations, 1939; 1939/717.F
      - Germany, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1330)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/717.S
      - Germany, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1330)
  - Hungary, 1939; 1939/750
    - Hungary, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1331)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/750.E
      - Hungary, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1331)
  - Italy, 1939; 1939/751
    - Italy, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1331)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/751.E
      - Italy, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
    - Italy - Public Health Education, 1939; 1939/751.L
      - Italy, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
  - Norway, 1939; 1939/767
    - Norway, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/767.E
      - Norway, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/767.R
      - Norway, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
    - Norway - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/767.S
      - Norway, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
  - Iran, 1939; 1939/771
    - Iran, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
  - Portugal, 1939; 1939/773
    - Portugal, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1332)
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/773.E
      - Portugal, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1333)
    - Portugal - Public Health Education, 1939; 1939/773.L
      - Portugal, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1333)
  - Romania, 1939; 1939/783
    - Romania, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1333)
    - Romania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/783.E
      - Romania, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1333)
  - USSR, 1939; 1939/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1333)
    - USSR - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/785.S
      - U.S.S.R., 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1333)
  - Latvia, 1939; 1939/786
    - Latvia, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
  - Finland, 1939; 1939/787
    - Finland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/787.E
      - Finland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
  - Lithuania, 1939; 1939/788
    - Lithuania, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
    - Lithuania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/788.E
      - Lithuania, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
  - Poland, 1939; 1939/789
    - Poland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/789.E
      - Poland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
  - Sweden, 1939; 1939/800
    - Sweden, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/800.E
      - Sweden, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/800.R
      - Sweden, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
  - Switzerland, 1939; 1939/803
    - Switzerland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
    - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1939; 1939/803.R
      - Switzerland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
    - Switzerland - Social Sciences, 1939; 1939/803.S
      - Switzerland, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1335)
  - Turkey, 1939; 1939/805
    - Turkey, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1336)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1939; 1939/805.E
      - Turkey, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1336)
  - Cyprus, 1939; 1939/809
    - Cyprus, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1336)
  - Lebanon, 1939; 1939/833
    - Lebanon, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 1336)